Nicholasdeveault@gmail.com

https://github.com/Nicholasdeveault

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nicholas-deveault/

Nicholas Deveault

About me

I am someone who is very imaginative, open-minded and curious, energized by social interaction and focusing on social harmony and cooperation. I am meticulous and highly organized making me a great asset to your team. I value clarity, structure and planning. Proven experience in mentorship, mediation and proven leadership in projects.

SKILLS

- JavaScript ES6, React.js, Node.js, Redux, MongoDB, CSS and HTML5.
- Currently learning: SEO, TypeScript, Firebase and Angular.js.

PROJECTS

Independent projects

2020 - now

- Development of a website for an independent enterprise in Montreal Club de Judo Hibagon - using these tools: JavaScript, React, Node.js, CSS and MongoDB.
- Project link: https://github.com/Nicholasdeveault/Judo-training-manager

Team project:

2021

- Development of a website for an E-Commerce online shop using these tools: JavaScript, React, Node.js, CSS and MongoDB.
- Project link: https://github.com/Nicholasdeveault/YYZ-TECH-E-Commerce

EDUCATION

Concordia University, Montreal - Full Stack Web Development

April 2021

• Technologies covered include: JavaScript ES6, React, Redux, Node.js, MongoDB, CSS, HTML5, Github and Visual Studio Code.

Codecademy - JavaScript certification

• Learning JavaScript basics to reinforce my knowledge.

freeCodeCamp - Responsive Web Design certification

September 2020

• Learning how to properly use and apply web design tools.

EXPERIENCE

Nisto, Montreal - Full Stack Web Developer

January 2021 - PRESENT

- Part-time.
- Start-up Web Development agency.

Nissan Canada, Longueuil - Sales representant

2019 - 2020

• Meeting with clients and selling products.

Jack & Jones, Saint-Bruno - 3rd key/Assistant manager in formation

2018 - 2019

• Retail sales, customer service and team leader.